▍2026 多伦多 WTA1000 第三轮
伊埃拉 6-3 5-7 6-4 麦克纳莉 · 赛后新闻发布会
Alex, congratulations on an incredible win.
亚历克斯 恭喜这场精彩的胜利
After the match, you kind of just sat there
赛后你坐在那儿
and just
就那样
Yeah. Can you explain that moment
能说说那一刻吗
and just what was going through your mind
你当时在想什么
and
还有
Yeah.
嗯
Yeah. Um I think this match
我觉得这场
was was really challenging for me.
对我来说真的很有挑战
I think the whole two weeks I guess
这整整两周
have been very challenging
都很有挑战
and each match that I've played
我打的每一场
has presented its unique set of challenges.
都有各自不同的难题
Um yeah, today obviously was really close
今天这场确实很胶着
and I think you know like I'm I'm
我
really of course I'm feeling the effects
确实感觉到了
of you know just everything
这一切带来的影响
and I think I'm really doing
我真的在尽力
my best like I said on court
就像我在场上说的那样
to um you know to stay professional
保持专业
and stick to what I know but everything
做我熟悉的事 但这一切
of course like this past two weeks I've
这两周我
been feeling emotions so extremely
情绪一直很强烈
because of the the circumstances
因为这些经历
which is which is a great thing.
这其实是件好事
You know, I love I'm I think I'm quite a
我觉得我是个
sentimental person.
挺重感情的人
Um but at the same time,
但同时
it's just kind of like finding that balance.
也在找一个平衡
So, I think um I'm really proud
所以我挺为自己骄傲
of how I handled today
今天处理得不错
and and and what I did on court.
场上的表现也是
Yeah, Alex, there there were so many times
亚历克斯 这场好多次
during the match where you were tested,
你都被逼到了极限
you know, you had to come up
你不得不
from early holes in the games.
从落后的局面里爬出来
What are you kind
你
of telling yourself in the moment uh
那种时候心里在想什么
when you're fighting back
当你从落后的比分里
from those early deficits and games?
往回拼的时候
Yeah, I think I need I try
我会
to focus more on factual things.
更专注在事实上
So, um I mean of course there
当然
are many external factors
有很多外部因素
but there are things that also I can control
但也有我能控制的部分
and I'm I was aware of the situation.
我很清楚当时的局面
I know that she was playing well.
我知道她打得很好
Um I know that I
我也知道我
was missing certain balls here and there.
有些球没处理好
So I tried to just play the point better
所以我就想把这一分打
than the point before.
得比上一分更好
Yeah.
嗯
Hi Alex, well done.
你好 亚历克斯 打得漂亮
So, the the Blue Dinosaur super fan
那个蓝色恐龙的超级粉丝
was back today.
今天又来了
Oh my gosh.
天呐
Oh my god. How just talk
天呐 说说
about your new super fan
你这位新粉丝吧
and how much are you noticing him,
你注意到他了吗
you know, throughout the
整场比赛
You know, today I didn't see him
其实今天我没看见他
in the crowd.
在人群里
I knew he I know he was there.
但我知道他在
People told me he was there.
有人跟我说他来了
Um but wow, what a legend.
他真的很传奇
Like it was so funny
第一晚我第一次看见他的时候
when I first saw him the first night.
真的太好笑了
Amazing. And I think it
真是 我是说
was just I don't know.
说不上来
It just it was like such a light funny spin
就是给大家支持我的方式
to kind of like how how people support me.
添了一种轻松好玩的调调
It just comes out in very unique ways
每个人支持的方式都很不一样
and I think he's really stood out.
他这个真的很突出